{
	"item": [{
		"question": "It serves as a tool that allows Web Servers and Web browsers to communicate",
		"answer": "HTTP"
	}, {
		"question": "What is the meaning of MIME?",
		"answer": "Multimedia-Purpose Internet Mail Extensions"
	}, {
		"question": "Allows responses to be stored in the methods for future use.",
		"answer": "Cacheable Methods"
	}, {
		"question": "A code used to indicate the status of the Clientâ€™s request.",
		"answer": "Status Code"
	}, {
		"question": "Provision that allows methods used for authoring the websites remotely.",
		"answer": "WebDAV"
	}, {
		"question": "It is used to identify the data type of the information being sent.",
		"answer": "MIME-TYPE"
	}, {
		"question": "A protocol wherein the Client initiates the transmission of Web resources by sending a request to the server.",
		"answer": "Request-Response Protocol"
	}, {
		"question": "Version of HTTP that supports data compression",
		"answer": "1.1"
	}, {
		"question": "It includes additional information regarding the Client.",
		"answer": "Header"
	}, {
		"question": "A method property that indicates no changes are done in the state of the Server.",
		"answer": "Safe method"
	}]
}